(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
GEORGE : THANK YOU...
THANK YOU VERY MUCH
WE'D LIKE TO CARRY ON NOW
WITH A SONG FROM OUR
NEW ALBUM IN ENGLAND
AND IT'LL BE OUT IN
AMERICA SHORTLY
AND IT'S A SONG WITH--
FEATURING JUST PAUL
AND IT'S CALLED 'YESTERDAY'
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)
♪ ♪
♪ YESTERDAY ♪
♪ ALL MY TROUBLES
SEEMED SO FAR AWAY. ♪
♪ NOW IT LOOKS AS THOUGH
THEY'RE HERE TO STAY. ♪
♪ OH, I BELIEVE
IN YESTERDAY. ♪
♪ SUDDENLY, ♪
♪ I'M NOT HALF THE
MAN I USED TO BE. ♪
♪ THERE'S A SHADOW
HANGING OVER ME. ♪
♪ OH, YESTERDAY
CAME SUDDENLY. ♪
♪ WHY SHE HAD TO GO? ♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW,
SHE WOULDN'T SAY. ♪
♪ I SAID SOMETHING WRONG. ♪
♪ NOW I LONG FOR YESTERDAY. ♪
♪ YESTERDAY ♪
♪ LOVE WAS SUCH AN
EASY GAME TO PLAY. ♪
♪ NOW I NEED A PLACE
TO HIDE AWAY. ♪
♪ OH, I BELIEVE
IN YESTERDAY. ♪
♪ WHY SHE HAD TO GO? ♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW,
SHE WOULDN'T SAY. ♪
♪ I SAID SOMETHING WRONG. ♪
♪ NOW I LONG FOR YESTERDAY. ♪
♪ YESTERDAY ♪
♪ LOVE WAS SUCH AN
EASY GAME TO PLAY. ♪
♪ NOW I NEED A PLACE
TO HIDE AWAY. ♪
♪ OH, I BELIEVE
IN YESTERDAY. ♪
♪ MM MM MM MM MM MM MM ♪
(AUDIENCE CHEERS)